Not not a heck of a lot of dramatic
news, but uh you know, passed a few
different plane roles and uh
you know, just a lot of other business,
but uh
nothing dramatic that I can share with
you. So.
Happy to answer any questions.
>> like the kind of whatever concession or
agreement that you have with the
replacement officials with New York
calling penalties?
Well, we passed the rule. Hopefully, we
don't have to use it. I mean, the goal
is to get an agreement done, so that's
about all I can say about it.
>> satisfied with it?
Yeah, I mean, the rule I I think the
rule will help if we need it. All right.
I know you guys weren't necessarily
negotiating 18 games at this point
because the CBA isn't out, but what are
your feelings on an 18-game schedule?
I mean, it really wasn't part of the
discussion. I think we have a way to go.
I mean, the the
uh
Players Association, you know, just uh
hired some new leadership, and I think
it'll take them a little while to
get the their feet on the ground and get
ready to go. So, I I I don't think
there's going to be any any news on that
front anytime soon.
Do you Do you anticipate any potential
changes to the Rooney Rule, and is it
important for you to preserve certain
aspects of it going forward? I You know,
I I don't think uh I I don't anticipate
any dramatic changes to the Rooney Rule.
Uh you know, we always are looking at
our uh employment policies and and uh
you know, every year we do we do an an
analysis of what we're doing and what we
can do to improve the situation, but uh
I don't expect any major changes to the
Rooney Rule. Or was there any discussion
about it? What in light of what the
Florida Yeah, we had a little discussion
about the Rooney Rule. There were some
questions about it. I mean, uh
you know, there's no There was no action
taken, just a statement from the Florida
Attorney General, so it's you know,
probably have some conversations with
the Attorney General down there just to
make sure he understands what exactly we
do. It's not a hiring rule.
Uh so, uh you know, I think we're
comfortable with where we are. What was
the general
uh discussion reaction support of the
other owners? And it Yeah, I I think
everybody's still in favor of the you
know, the Rooney Rule. There's no no
discussion about you know, getting rid
of it, that's for sure.
All right. Is [snorts] there uh any
update that you've talked with I feel
like this is a yearly tradition at this
point, but with Aaron Rodgers, have you
talked with him recently or have any
kind of anticipated timeline on when you
might get a decision from him?
I I have not talked to him. Uh coach has
been in contact with him pretty
regularly, and uh I think the decision's
probably coming soon. Do you anticipate
hearing one way or the other by the NFL
draft?
I would say by the draft, I expect an
answer, yep.
How are the preparations coming for the
draft, and uh what what's got you
excited about that right now? Yeah, I
mean, it's the preparations are coming
good. I think uh people are now going to
start to see things coming out of the
ground on the North Shore, and and uh
so, it's it's going to be an exciting
time, and we're really looking forward
to it. I trust your proposal from last
year was made permanent about the uh
talking to
>> Yes. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Anyone else?
>> at the stadium, is that something that
new colors, is that something that was
just added
about it for a while, anything like
that?
Yeah, as we were making changes to the
the seating, uh you know, the the sea of
gold sometimes gets overwhelming, so we
did add a little black and gold in there
this time around. And where are you guys
in the process of the new field blend,
the the playing surface? Is that being
planted right now, just kind of where
where are you guys at?
>> Well, the the field's actually will be
planted at a at a sod farm, so we won't
get the new field until sometime in
August. But, you know, as we've talked
about, it'll be a new surface, a new
kind of grass mixture, and
you know, look forward to having seeing
how it works. Was that something that
was mandated by the league or or or No.
No,
we we chose to make the change. Wasn't
mandated by the league, so uh
it's it's been in use in some other
stadiums around the country, and it
seems to be having success, so we
decided to make the change.
>> Is there any pattern to the seat designs
of putting the black in?
Uh no, it's it's it's a random pattern.
Yeah, okay. It doesn't spell out
anything.
>> No, there's no no spelling to it, no.
All right.
>> All right, man. All right, thanks,
everybody.
>> and out.